I couldn't find anything
about Bea's father
or her family.
[BILLY] I'm not done with Abi.
[BEA] Billy said I was a thief.
But she's the original thief herself!
[BILLY] You and Oliver
could've gotten hurt!
I won't let that slide.
She messed with the wrong person.
[PRECIOUS] Billy.
What's that?
Enrico's letters?
This is a lot.
He didn't forget
about us after all, Auntie.
[DOCTOR] But upon further evaluation
of your condition,
you are in an advanced stage
of heart failure.
Doc, have you told my family?
Ah, not yet.
Doc, please.
Don't tell them.
Your family needs to know
that some of your arteries are blocked.
Enrico, you will have
to tell them sooner or later.
You'll need surgery.
[PHONE RINGING]
Jordan?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello?
[JORDAN] Dude?
I'm here at your house.
They've recovered some of your things.
Would you like to see?
[MARIELA] I'm sorry, dear.
I've become even more of a burden to you.
You're my mother.
Okay?
You'll never be a burden to me.
You're the only family I have.
I'd do anything for you.
I'm not.
You still have a father.
The thing is,
we're not important to him anymore.
Is that jerk still alive?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MONITOR BEEPING]
Oh…
- Ma?
- Hmm?
- Can I take the front seat?
- Nuh-uh.
- [MARIELA] You can't.
- Okay then.
You can sit there.
[MARIELA GRUNTS]
Okay?
[ENGINE STARTS]
- Let's go!
- Ready?
- We're ready!
- Where do you want to go?
First stop.
A convenience store.
- Convenience store! Let's go!
- My goodness.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[HURRIED FOOTSTEPS]
[BILLY] Bea!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
Where do you think you're going?
- Damn you!
- [BEA GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BEA SCREAMING]
Get off me!
You witch!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BEA SCREAMS]
[THUDS, PANTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [SCREAMS]
[BILLY PANTING, SCREAMS]
What do you want, huh?
Is this what you want?
- Damn you, you witch! [SLAP LANDS]
- [BEA GROANING]
What more do you want from me, huh?!
- Leave us alone!
- [SLAPS LANDING]
Leave us alone! Damn you!
Billy! Billy!
[SHRIEKS]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS] Billy!
- [PANTING]
- [BEA CHOKING] Billy--
[PRECIOUS] Billy! Billy!
- That's enough!
- [GUARD] Ma'am, that's enough!
- Billy, come on!
- Ma'am, please stop!
- Billy! Billy!
- [SOBBING] Leave us alone!
- [PRECIOUS] Enough, Billy.
- [BEA PANTING]
What, huh?!
You'll pay for this.
- You and your mother will pay.
- That's enough!
It'll be jail time for you.
[BILLY] I'll make sure of it.
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Yo.
Boss.
Pulled an all-nighter?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
What's that? Still trying to locate
the LoveLine hacker?
This is the only way I can help Billy.
You know what else you could do?
Tell Billy your true feelings.
[ROBBIE] There you go! Am I right?
- [ROBBIE LAUGHS]
- Now?
With everything that's going on,
you're telling me to confess?
No.
No, Robbie.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I don't want to add to her problems.
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- [GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Dude.
[BILLY] Dude.
I need your help.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
[BILLY] I'm Billy Cariño.
Mariela Mercado is your mother, correct?
I told you, yes. We've been
going at it since earlier.
Where is she?
[SIGHS] I told you, I don't know!
You've had a record here before,
Marie Beatrice Mercado.
But out on bail.
[BEA] Exactly. So you know.
You can't just detain me for no reason.
Your previous case is a different story.
But this complaint against your mother--
Ma'am, I don't know anything. Okay?
What are you going to do?
I don't know anything.
You'll detain me? You can't do that.
That's illegal because you don't
have a warrant.
Isn't that right?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES OMINOUS]
[BEA] Can I go now?
[POLICE] Yes, Ms. Bea Mercado.
Thank you. You can go now.
Oh, miss, get me away from her.
See? She's getting closer.
She'll punch me again.
She did this to me.
Get her away from me.
Why is she still out here?
We can't detain her
because there's no evidence
that she's an accomplice
in burning your property, Ms. Cariño.
I overlooked her being released many times
because I respect your due process.
But who knows? Arson might not be
all she'll do next time.
She might just murder us.
Me?!
How dramatic. I'm not a bad person.
I'm not a murderer.
Uh, Ms. Cariño,
our search for Mariela Mercado
is still ongoing.
Trust that we'll contact you immediately
as soon as we have any news about her.
[POLICE] Excuse me.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you sure you want to get out?
You might regret it.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
They just let Bea go?!
Yes, Auntie Pres.
But don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
What? What happened?
I'm tired of getting my hopes
up for nothing, Auntie.
So I'll put a stop to them myself.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEA] Ah, sir.
Bring me to this hotel.
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Billy!
- Hi.
- Jordan!
Hi.
What brings you here?
Um…
Someone tried to leak
our confidential data.
Confidential data?
[BILLY] Yes.
Transcript of LoveLine calls
along with other sensitive information
about our members.
But fortunately,
we have upgraded
our cybersecurity system,
so we are good.
Th-that's good.
Should I be worried?
No.
[LINE RINGING]
Hello, Jordan? Where are you?
Summit Bay Suites.
We've been here before.
This is where Peter was staying.
This can't be a coincidence.
Why?
This is where I traced the location
of the person who leaked LoveList's files.
Okay. I'm going there.
Okay.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Wilfred.
Your and your mom's passports
and birth certificates are ready.
Here. Take a look.
Okay. Thank you. I'll pick them up later.
Wait. You are too excited.
Do you have the money yet?
No money, no documents.
You won't get the passport, okay?
I'll get it later, okay?
So wait for me.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma.
Pack your things. We're leaving.
Huh?
We'll leave now.
We're going to Taiwan.
I have a friend there.
They will help us start a new life.
Come on! Pack now!
So this means
that you accept that you lost
to your father's illegitimate daughter?
You're going to run away?
Ma, what are you talking about?
I'm doing this for you!
Will we be the losers again, Bea?
This is all because of me!
I dragged you into this!
No! We haven't lost!
How do we get revenge if we leave?
Ma, please,
can we think about revenge later?
If they find you, if they put you in jail,
that's when we lose!
Please, let's just pack up and leave.
Dude. Where is she?
- I lost her.
- Huh?!
She suddenly disappeared!
I'm sorry. I asked reception,
but they don't want to tell me anything.
How did you lose her, Jordan?
Sorry.
Wait. Dude.
Is that Peter?
I'm at the lobby. Meet me here.
No. I'm not going down there.
Get up here.
What?! Are you--
[WHISPERING] Bea, are you serious?!
You better keep your word, Bea.
Delete the photo once you get the money,
and then don't ever bother me again!
We know it was you, Peter.
Remember the leaked files?
It was uploaded from this hotel.
[BILLY] You were talking to Bea.
Bea Mercado, right?
What's your connection to her?
Did she force you to steal our files?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Her mother's on the run.
And we know she's hiding her here.
Just tell us the truth.
It'll make things a lot easier for you.
We heard your conversation with Bea.
Is she blackmailing you?
[BILLY] You're a lawyer, Peter.
You know what you did.
You also know that it's a crime
even if you acted out of coercion.
Now, if you cooperate,
we can handle this properly.
If not, I will have you arrested,
and things will get ugly.
Is that what you want?
I'll tell you everything.
Ma, I'm done packing!
What about your things?
That's the only thing you'll bring?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Who's that?
What else?
That's our way out.
Pack your things now, okay?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Ma'am, we need your cooperation!
We know you're inside!
- Oh! Why?
- Ma. Shh!
- [WHISPERING] Who's that?
- Be quiet!
[WHISPERING] Billy's outside!
She's with the police!
Oh no! Oh no!
What are we going to do?!
Open it.
- What are we going to do?!
- Wait!
I'll think! I'll think!
[BREATHING HEAVILY] We've got to get out!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BEA] Sir, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
Mariela Mercado, we have
a warrant for your arrest.
Go away!
We are charging you
with qualified trespass to dwelling,
frustrated murder, and reckless
imprudence resulting in arson.
- Go ahead, cuff her!
- Sir, wait a minute!
Wait! Arrest me instead!
Spare my mother!
Take me instead! Please!
- You're all animals!
- Ma, no!
Cuff her!
Billy, please! Not my mother!
Take me instead!
- Billy!
- Cuff her!
[BEA] Ma…
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What? Are you scared?
Don't worry.
Your daughter will be with you in jail.
[CUFF CLICKS]
We'll be the ones messing
with your life this time.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES,
FADES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Dude.
Finally!
It's over!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Damn you!
[MARIELA] You are the ones who
should go to prison instead!
You should pay!
I'll get back at you,
especially you, Billy.
I'll get back at you, you bastard!
[OFFICER] That's enough. Take her in.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PRECIOUS] They're both
in jail now. Thank God.
[BILLY] I have a lot I need to recover.
[BEA] No matter what happens,
don't tell them
that you know
they are Papa's second family.
That's the truth.
It'll just prove that you're
going after Papa's illegitimate child.
And Oliver will stay there.
As well as Dad.
You're letting your father
live here with us?
Are you sure about this?
Your father
is asking about the fire.
He wants to know what really happened.
[BEA] I will do
everything possible, Ma.
I will do everything I can
to get you out of here.
Not just me.
Both of us.
I found these.
I've read all of them too.
Would it be okay
if I asked for a hug?
I don't know if Billy will ever
be able to forgive me
for what I'm about to tell her.
FIRE BURNS DOWN HOME
I know this is too much.
But she needs to know the truth.
I'm sorry.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]